<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Helios Messenger</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About Helios Messenger</string>
    <string name="pref_report_crashes_summary">Help us improve Helios Messenger by sending your crash logs to the development team. Please find detailed information about crash reports in our FAQ.</string>
    <string name="dialog_report_crash_message">Crash information available. We kindly ask you to send this information to Helios Messenger developers and help us improving our service.</string>
    <string name="dialog_report_errors_message">Error information available. We kindly ask you to send this information to Helios Messenger developers and help us improving our service.</string>
    <string name="sms_invitation_text">Hey! I\'m now using the free app Helios Messenger for secure chatting. Download it now and add me as a contact:\n%1$s%2$s\n%3$s</string>
    <string name="email_invitation_subject">Join me at Helios Messenger!</string>
    <string name="email_invitation_text">Hey!I\'m now using the free app Helios Messenger for secure chatting. Download it now and add me as contact:\n%1$s%2$s\n%3$s</string>
    <string name="actionbar_default_title">Helios</string>
    <string name="about_advert_text">Helios Messenger \n- your secure multimedia messenger\n\nSecurity, data protection and the protection of privacy are of extreme importance to us. Helios Messenger sets new standards in mobile data transmission and puts mobile privacy to a whole new level, due to latest encryption and transmission technologies. Helios Messenger provides an easy and unlimited exchange of data between smartphones and tablets, without constraining users to register and enter confidential data.\n\nShare hugs \u0026 kisses</string>
    <string name="restore_restart_hoccer">Please re-start Helios Messenger to complete restoring your account. </string>
    <string name="restore_no_backups_found_message">Please copy a backup to\n%1$s\nto restore a former Helios Messenger account.</string>

    <string name="placeholder_conversations_text"><![CDATA[<a href="http://faq.hoccer.com/helios/tutorial-xo/#invite">Invite friends</a>]]> to chat with!</string>
    <string name="placeholder_groups_text"><![CDATA[<a href="http://faq.hoccer.com/helios/tutorial-xo/#groups">Create groups</a>]]> to chat with many friends at once.</string>
    <string name="placeholder_nearby_text">Waiting for others <![CDATA[<a href="http://faq.hoccer.com/helios/tutorial-xo/#nearby">nearby</a>]]>…</string>
    <string name="placeholder_worldwide_text">Waiting for others <![CDATA[<a href="http://faq.hoccer.com/helios/tutorial-xo/#worldwide">worldwide</a>]]>…</string>

    <!-- Tutorial and FAQ links -->
    <string name="link_tutorial">http://faq.hoccer.com/helios/tutorial-xo/</string>
    <string name="link_faq">http://faq.hoccer.com/helios/</string>

</resources>
